>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这是一个例子
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Here's
an example that tries to
指出这不是一个快照
point out that it's not a snapshot.
这也是开发者似乎一直感到沮丧的其中之一。
And this is one of the perpetual
frustrations that developers seem to have.
他们知道这个想法，好封闭，然后马上就跳了
They get this idea, okay closure,
but then they immediately jump
这意味着我将会有一个价值
to the assumption that that means
that I'm snapshoting a value.
我正在捕捉一些有价值的信息
That I'm capturing some
value at some moment.
这不是关闭的原因。
That is not what closure is.
事实上，关闭与这些价值根本没有关系。
Closure has not got anything to do with
the values at all, as a matter of fact.
您不会关闭值。
You don't close over a value.
我在博客和书中见过无数次
I've seen that countless
times in blogs and books.
没有这样的事情，胡说八道，
There is no such thing, that is nonsense,
没有关闭一个价值的东西
there's no such thing as
closing over a value.
您可以关闭变量，这意味着您与该变量具有链接。
You close over a variable, which means
you have a linkage to that variable.
当你进入它的时候
Which means at the time you access it,
你可以看到任何变量在那一刻所产生的价值，而不是以前的。
you're seeing whatever value that variable
has at that moment, not it had before.
在此示例中，当我在第 3 行上创建 myTeacher 函数时，
Here in this example when I create
the myTeacher function on line 3,
那一刻老师的价值是凯尔的
at that moment teacher has the value Kyle.
后来我改变了老师对苏西的价值
And then later I change
teacher to the value Suzy.
然后当我执行它要打印的功能时，第 9 行吗 ?
And then line 9 when I execute
the function what's it gonna print?
不是凯尔，我们没有接近凯尔的价值，我们关闭了变量老师。
Not Kyle, we didn't close over the value
Kyle, we closed over the variable teacher.
当我们执行这一功能时，我们会获得它的价值。
And when we execute that function,
we're gonna access the value of it.
它是对您关闭的所有变量的实时链接。
It is a live link to all the variables
that you are closed over.
所以不要把关闭视为捕获值，
So don't think of closure
as capturing values,
将其视为保留对变量的访问权。
think of it as preserving
access to variables.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 最经典的人最经典的地方
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The place where this
bites people the most, the most classic
规范示例，每当您尝试在 for 循环中创建闭包，或
canonical example, is whenever you try to
create closures inside of a for loop, or
任何循环机构的内部。
inside of any kind of looping mechanism.
通常不与计时器有关，但这只是一个方便的插图。
Not usually with timers, but that's
just a convenient illustration here.
通常，它就像将单击处理程序指定给一组按钮以进行
Normally it's like assigning click
handlers to an array of buttons for
示例。
example.
并且这个函数是在每个迭代中创建的，它具有外观
And this function, that is being created
in each iteration, it has the appearance
每一个迭代中的值都要接近我的值。
that what it's doing is closing
over the i value in each iteration.
所以我们希望它能打印出我的 1
So we're expecting it to print out i 1,
i 2, i 3, but
当我们把它打印出来的时候就有四，四，四，四，四，四，四，
when we run it it prints out 4, 4, 4.
为甚么呢 ?
Why?
库兹只有一个我的变量
Cuz there's only one i variable.
第 1 行有一个变量只有一个变量
There's an i variable on line 1 and
there's only one of them, and
我们有三个功能
we have three functions.
如果我们想有三个不同的价值观，我们需要多少变数呢 ?
If we wanted to have three separate
values, how many variables would we need?
这不是很难的数学。
This is not hard math.
如果我们想要三个不同的值，我们需要多少个变量 ?
If we wanted three separate values,
how many variables do we need?
我们需要三个变量对吧
We need three variables, right?
而且只有一个，当然它只能有一个价值。
And there's only one, so
of course it can only have the one value.
在这种情况下它会有一个价值
And in this case,
it's gonna have the value that occurs
在循环的末尾，是值 4。
at the end of the loop,
which is the value 4.
我们不能有效地使用封闭装置直到我们独立
We can't effectively use closure
until we separate ourselves from that
捕获值的感知。
perception of capturing values.
它没有捕获值，保留对变量的访问权 ?
It's not capturing a value,
preserving access to a variable, okay?
因此，如果我们想解决这个问题，
So, if we wanted to solve this problem,
and
我们分析了，我需要单独的变量，我们已经看到
we analyzed that,
I need separate variables, we've seen
如何创建变量的多个不同示例。
several multiple different examples
of how to create variables.
如果要创建多个同名变量，请执行以下步骤 :
If we wanna create more than one
variable with the same name,
我们需要做新的工作对吧
we need to make new scopes, right?
所以我们可以在这里做一个很重要的工作，但现在我们有了 6 个展览，
So we could do an iffy here, but the much
more common way now that we have ES six,
现在我们有了封锁范围
now that we have blockscoping,
只是在迭代中粘贴块作用域声明。
is to just stick a block scoped
declaration in the iteration.
因此，现在，让 j 在每次 4 循环迭代时运行。
So now let j is going to run
every time the 4 loop iterates.
它将在这个循环的整个新迭代中创造一个全新的 j
And it's gonna create a whole new j in
that whole new iteration of the loop.
当我们在第 4 行上结束时，我们正在关闭一个全新的 j。
When we close over it on line 4,
we are closing over a whole new j.
有三个单独的 js ，因此，我们会获得其中 1， 2和 3的值。
There are three separate js and therefore
we get the values in them 1, 2, and 3.
请参阅 " 捕获值 " 和 " 结束变量" 之间的差异 ?
See the difference between capturing
a value and closing over a variable?
我觉得有些人甚至会说更棘手的问题
It turns out there's an even, I think
better some people might say trickier, but
有更好的办法解决这个问题
there's an even better way
of solving this problem.
因为我一直在为 var i 和
Because that perpetual problem
of I'm doing for var i and
我的关闭不是在捕捉价值
my closures aren't capturing the value.
这对 JavaScript 开发者造成了 20 年的问题。
That's been a problem for
JavaScript developers for like 20 years.
他们决定用 iOS 6 来决定我们为什么不去
They decided with iOS six, well,
why don't we just go ahead and
所以如果你想让你的人
make it so
that if you use a let on your for
循环，我们将自动为每个迭代创建一个新的 i 。
loop we'll automatically create
a new i for each iteration.
而不是仅仅创造一个属于全人类的
Instead of creating just one
that belongs to the whole for
在这里每次迭代都有一个全新的全新 i
loop here there's gonna be
a brand new i for each iteration.
这意味着闭关闭厂好吗
Which means the closure
just magically works, okay?
重点是您需要对您关闭多个不同值
The point is if you need multiple
different values being closed over you
需要多个不同的变量。
need multiple different variables.
您需要关闭不同的变量，而不是尝试捕获值。
You need to close over different
variables, not try to capture values.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yes?
>> 扬声器 2: 所以，我实际上是在里面定义的，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So,
the i is defined actually inside,
虽然是这样写的，但是它实际上是在块里面定义的吗 ?
even though it's written this way, but is
it actually then defined inside the block?
这就是它的本质吗
Is that basically what it is?
>> 键盘 Simpson: 是，它被解释为每个迭代都有一个新的
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yes, it is interpreted
as if each iteration there's a new
声明 i，并且 JavaScript 负责为其指定值
declaration of i, and JavaScript takes
care of assigning it the value that it
它的表弟在上一次迭代结束时就有了
had that its cousin had at the end
of the previous iteration.
把所有东西都给你
It wires up all that stuff for you.
>> 扬声器 3: 是否还有其他情况适用，或者
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Is there any other
case were that applies as well or
是唯一的吗
is that the only one?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 所有 for 循环表单都有一个方差。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All of the for
loop forms have a for let variance.
所以在这里我们得让他知道
So for here, we have for let of.
我们已经允许， >> 演讲者 4: 每个人 ?
We have let,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Each?
>> Kyle Simpson: 嗯，对于每个都不是语法形式。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Well, for
each isn't a syntactic form.
这是一个迭代器，所以你已经有了这个功能。
That's a iterator, so
you already get a function with that one.
>> Kyle Simpson: [COUGH] 但是对，对于，对于这三种语法而言，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: [COUGH] But yeah, for,
for of, and for in, those three syntactic
对于循环，自动在迭代中进行其任务。
for loops automatically make their
thing inside of the iteration.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 顺便说一下，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: By the way,
just as a little tiny detail,
不是很多人都要穿过这条
not that many people
are gonna run across this.
但如果你想用一个公寓
But if you did try to use a const there,
您将会收到错误，因为 i++ 正在尝试修改变量。
you're gonna get an error because that
i++ is trying to modify the variable.
因此，您需要使用 let。
So here you would need to use a let.
所以封闭才是
So closure is a preservation
of the linkage
变量，而不是值的捕获。
to a variable,
not the capturing of the value.